Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Queen of Attack=
=ملكة الهجوم=
=Episode 11=
=الحلقة 11=
You don't look well.
أنت لا تبدو بخير.
How about letting me check your pulse?
ماذا عن السماح لي بالتحقق من نبضك؟
You can read the pulse?
هل يمكنك قراءة النبض؟
That's great!
هذا رائع!
Her Highness will take you into the mansion.
صاحبة السمو ستأخذك إلى القصر.
Find a way to lose those Xu family followers.
ابحث عن طريقة للتخلص من أتباع عائلة Xu.
Return to the capital and enter the mansion.
العودة إلى العاصمة والدخول إلى القصر.
Your condition isn't ordinary.
حالتك ليست عادية.
Father, Mother,
الأب، الأم،
that gentleman said I'm unwell.
قال ذلك الرجل أنني مريض.
He wants to treat me inside.
يريد أن يعالجني داخليا.
What?
ماذا؟
You...
أنت...
Are you out of your mind?
هل أنت خارج عقلك؟
Father! Mother!
أبي! أمي!
I don't care! I'm going anyway!
لا يهمني! سأذهب على أي حال!
You're asking for trouble!
أنت تطلب المتاعب!
Disgraceful girl.
فتاة مخزية.
Get back here!
العودة إلى هنا!
My dear,
عزيزي،
don't hit her!
لا تضربها!
Something's wrong. After them!
هناك خطب ما. بعدهم!
(Posthouse)
(مكتب البريد)
Mother,
الأم،
why don't we live in a mansion like this?
لماذا لا نعيش في قصر مثل هذا؟
No! I want to live here too!
لا! أريد أن أعيش هنا أيضًا!
Alright!
على ما يرام!
(Luo Family's testimony) This is the Luo family's testimony.
(شهادة عائلة لوه) هذه شهادة عائلة لوه.
I thought they came to clear my name.
اعتقدت أنهم جاءوا لتبرئة اسمي.
Turns out they fabricated false testimony.
اتضح أنهم قدموا شهادة زور.
They claimed I'd been estranged from my parents.
لقد زعموا أنني كنت منفصلاً عن والدي.
They said I disobeyed my family
قالوا إنني عصيت عائلتي
and accused me of plotting patricide.
واتهمني بالتخطيط لقتل والدي.
They were crucial witnesses.
لقد كانوا شهودًا مهمين.
Without their testimonies,
بدون شهاداتهم،
your conviction wouldn't have been secured so fast.
لم يكن من الممكن أن يتم تأمين إدانتك بهذه السرعة.
Uncle,
عم،
Aunt,
عمة،
Qing,
تشينغ،
my apologies.
اعتذاري.
I forgot about you before.
لقد نسيتك من قبل.
How did the Luos enter the mansion?
كيف دخل اللوو إلى القصر؟
Indeed.
بالفعل.
It should be okay, right?
يجب أن يكون على ما يرام، أليس كذلك؟
This escape attempt
محاولة الهروب هذه
was meant to pressure the County Princess
كان الهدف منه الضغط على أميرة المقاطعة
into formally recognizing me.
إلى الاعتراف بي رسميًا.
Didn't she already
ألم تكن بالفعل
bring your family here?
هل ستحضر عائلتك هنا؟
That counts as acknowledgment.
وهذا يعد بمثابة اعتراف.
Let's get back to the mansion first.
دعونا نعود إلى القصر أولاً.
Come on.
تعال.
This one is delicious.
هذا لذيذ.
Truth be told,
الحقيقة هي أن
frankly speaking,
بصراحة،
when I first heard your story,
عندما سمعت قصتك لأول مرة،
none of us
لا أحد منا
believed it.
اعتقدت ذلك.
That shameless Hong'er...
تلك هونغ إير الوقحة...
Ziyi.
إنهم كذلك.
Hong'er...
هونغ إير...
Hong'er is her childhood name.
هونغ إير هو اسمها في طفولتها.
What's good about her?
ما هو الجيد فيها؟
She's not ladylike at all.
إنها ليست سيدة على الإطلاق.
When I
عندما انا
arranged her marriage to Mr. Sun,
رتبت زواجها من السيد صن،
her father groveled in gratitude.
زحف والدها في امتنان.
She was unmarriageable otherwise.
كانت غير صالحة للزواج بخلاف ذلك.
Tell me. How can she compare
أخبرني كيف يمكنها المقارنة
to our Qing?
إلى تشينغ لدينا؟
Look.
ينظر.
Beautiful as blossoms,
جميلة كالزهور
divine as a goddess,
إلهية كإلهة،
skilled in song and dance.
ماهر في الغناء والرقص.
Look.
ينظر.
Take a look!
إلق نظرة!
How could she possibly attract
كيف يمكنها أن تجتذب؟
nobility like you?
نبلاء مثلك؟
How can we possibly feel no hatred?
كيف يمكننا أن لا نشعر بالكراهية؟
Father,
أب،
you're drunk.
أنت في حالة سكر.
Stop drinking.
توقف عن الشرب.
I'm not drunk.
أنا لست في حالة سكر.
Father.
أب.
Not drunk.
ليس سكرانًا.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
I'm not drunk.
أنا لست في حالة سكر.
Uncle.
عم.
Hong'er?
هونغ'ر؟
No.
لا.
- Uncle. - It's Ziyi.
- عمي. - إنه زيي.
Ziyi?
ما هم؟
Then you're Hong'er?
إذن أنت هونغ إير؟
Hong'er.
هونغ'ر.
Hong'er,
هونغ إير،
you've changed?
هل تغيرت؟
Hong'er.
هونغ'ر.
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
I won't rest even as a ghost
لن أرتاح حتى كشبح
until I make your family pay.
حتى أجعل عائلتك تدفع الثمن.
I've wronged you.
لقد ظلمتك.
I've wronged your family.
لقد ظلمت عائلتك.
Uncle, you've drunk too much.
عمي، لقد شربت كثيرًا.
- You're drunk. - You've drunk too much.
- أنت في حالة سُكر. - لقد شربت كثيرًا.
- Aunt. - Father, you're drunk.
- عمتي. - أبي أنت سكران.
Help him back, hurry.
ساعده على العودة، بسرعة.
I've wronged you.
لقد ظلمتك.
Come on.
تعال.
- I've wronged you. - You're drunk!
- لقد ظلمتك. - أنت سكران!
I've wronged you.
لقد ظلمتك.
Who are you really?
من أنت حقا؟
Why won't you look at me?
لماذا لا تنظر إلي؟
I'm not.
انا لست كذلك.
From our very first meeting,
منذ أول لقاء لنا،
you've avoided looking at me.
لقد تجنبت النظر إلي.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
what exactly do you want?
ماذا تريد بالضبط؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I don't know what I want to do.
لا أعلم ماذا أريد أن أفعل.
But these crazy thoughts
ولكن هذه الأفكار المجنونة
keep popping into my head.
تظل تظهر في ذهني.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Aren't you crazy?
ألا أنت مجنون؟
The child in my womb
الطفل في بطني
should sober you up now.
ينبغي أن يجعلك واعيًا الآن.
Move.
يتحرك.
Move!
يتحرك!
Do you want to drag us all to death?
هل تريد أن تجرنا جميعا إلى الموت؟
Well...
حسنًا...
I just want money.
أريد المال فقط.
You want money?
هل تريد المال؟
Didn't my father pay you?
ألم يدفع لك والدي؟
Your father did pay me,
لقد دفع لي والدك،
but now that I'm in the mansion,
ولكن الآن بعد أن أصبحت في القصر،
my price naturally goes up.
سعرى يرتفع بشكل طبيعي.
Price goes up?
السعر يرتفع؟
Fine.
بخير.
I'd like to hear your new demand.
أريد أن أسمع طلبك الجديد.
Five thousand taels.
خمسة آلاف تايل.
Are you insane?
هل انت مجنون؟
Where would I get that much?
من أين أحصل على هذا القدر؟
Well...
حسنًا...
If your family can't afford it,
إذا لم تتمكن عائلتك من تحمل تكاليف ذلك،
how did you distort truth to sacrifice
كيف حرفت الحقيقة للتضحية
so many innocent lives
الكثير من الأرواح البريئة
and sit high as the Princess Consort?
وتجلس عاليا كزوجة الأميرة؟
Shut up!
اسكت!
Well...
حسنًا...
Fine.
بخير.
I agree.
أنا موافق.
Give me fifteen days.
أعطني خمسة عشر يوما.
I'll write home
سأكتب إلى المنزل
to have my father send the money.
لكي يرسل لي والدي المال.
Fifteen days?
خمسة عشر يوما؟
Very well.
جيد جدا.
Then we'll stay here those fifteen days.
ثم سنبقى هنا تلك الخمسة عشر يومًا.
When the money arrives,
عندما يصل المال،
we'll leave immediately.
سوف نغادر على الفور.
You...
أنت...
These are nice.
هذه جميلة.
Stop!
قف!
Alright.
على ما يرام.
This dress doesn't suit you anyway.
هذا الفستان لا يناسبك على أية حال.
Qing would suit it better.
تشينغ سوف يناسبها بشكل أفضل.
I'm leaving. Thanks.
سأغادر. شكرا.
(I need to eliminate this threat quickly)
(أحتاج إلى القضاء على هذا التهديد بسرعة)
(before complications arise.)
(قبل أن تظهر المضاعفات.)
- Look! - See these?
- انظر! - هل ترى هؤلاء؟
These are all fine stuff.
هذه كلها أشياء جميلة.
Mother,
الأم،
look!
ينظر!
The fabric,
القماش
and the embroidery...
والتطريز...
So exquisite.
رائعة للغاية.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Father, Mother,
الأب، الأم،
don't you think
ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
if I dress like her,
إذا ارتديت مثلها،
people wouldn't tell us apart?
الناس لن يفرقونا؟
Well...
حسنًا...
Father,
أب،
haven't you always said
ألم تقل دائما
had Master Xian met me first,
لو التقى بي السيد شيان أولاً،
I'd be the Princess Consort now?
هل سأكون الأميرة الزوجة الآن؟
I think Qing's no less than her.
أعتقد أن تشينغ ليس أقل منها.
Yes,
نعم،
exactly.
بالضبط.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Your Highness?
صاحب السمو؟
You fool!
يا أحمق!
How dare you seduce His Highness!
كيف تجرؤ على إغواء سموه!
What are you
ماذا انت
doing?
عمل؟
I...
أنا...
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Your Highness, save me!
صاحب السمو، أنقذني!
She hit me!
لقد ضربتني!
- I don't know what I did wrong. - What's all this?
- لا أعلم ما الخطأ الذي ارتكبته. - ما كل هذا؟
What's going on here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Do you know
هل تعلم
that framing someone to death
أن إيقاع شخص ما في الفخ حتى الموت
makes accomplice and instigator equally guilty.
يجعل الشريك والمحرض مذنبين على حد سواء.
Both must die.
كلاهما يجب أن يموتا.
She was trying to silence me!
لقد كانت تحاول إسكاتي!
I didn't!
لم أكن!
Silence her?
إسكاتها؟
♪Fate begins and ends, I sip the past♪
???القدر يبدأ وينتهي، أنا أرتشف الماضي؟؟؟
♪Love and hatred flow endlessly♪
???الحب والكراهية يتدفقان بلا نهاية؟؟؟
♪When spring comes, I see the truth♪
???عندما يأتي الربيع أرى الحقيقة؟؟؟
♪We've changed through the years♪
???لقد تغيرنا عبر السنين؟؟؟
♪Cold lamps reflect pear blossom dew♪
???المصابيح الباردة تعكس ندى زهرة الكمثرى ???
♪Worlds change as streams run west♪
???تتغير العوالم عندما تتدفق المجاري المائية غربًا؟؟؟
♪Rains veil hills, gathering sorrows♪
???أمطار تحجب التلال، وتجمع الأحزان؟؟؟
♪In deep courtyards, hands drift apart♪
???في الساحات العميقة، تتباعد الأيدي؟؟؟